http://www.adamant.com/privacy-policy

My Account
Register
Log in
Shopping cart
(0)
Wishlist
(0)
216 360 8877
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Shopping Cart
Shopping Cart
No items added.
View all
Adamant Technical Services online Personal Privacy Statement
In general, you can visit Adamant Online Store without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. However, there are times when we may need information from you, such as your name, address and e-mail address. Typically, we request your personal information only when you:
Order a product online
Apply for Reseller Status
Request e-mail confirmation of your order
Request a quote, tracking information or other specific information
Subscribe to receive FAX specials
Subscribe to our mailing list
Please Note: Your personal data is for Adamant's internal use only. We DO NOT give or sell your information or e-mail address to other individuals or companies.
All information you provide is kept confidential, as well as the specific products which you have purchased. It is Adamant's strict policy that NONE of your personal data (name, address, phone, FAX, e-mail address, etc.) will ever be disclosed or sold to any outside company or indivdual. Your personal information will never be used for any purpose without your permission.
Internet Sales Adamant Online Store was created to give you complete control and maintain strict security over the personal information you provide. To keep your information private we use state-of-the-art, industry-standard security procedures available through your Web browser, known as SSL Encryption. For more information about security, please check our Online Security Notice.
While Adamant Technical Services, Inc. will never give or sell your personal information to an outside company, we may use it to contact you in case of a problem with your order or to provide you with additional information about our products and services, after you subscribe to our mail.
If, at any time, you want your personal information to be removed from our company database, please contact us, and we will remove this information from our data files. Please note: Sales Invoices will remain in our company database, and a printed copy remains on file to maintain company records for inventory audits.
For any questions about your online privacy please send e-mail to
CustomerService@adamant.com.
Newsletter
Sign up for our newsletter:
Wait...
Copyright © 2020 Adamant Online Store. All rights reserved.
